<?xml version="1.0" encoding="windows-1252"?>
<news>
  <banner><![CDATA[<p>Fundraising Update:
To meet our budget, we need to raise $1,330 a day for the next 16 days. So far today we've raised $492, and for the month $18,875. We still are trying to raise $21,124 more by the end of the month.
</p>
]]>
  </banner>
  <items>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[New items for our supporters: A warm fleece zip sweatshirt we call the <a href="/support/unhoodie/">Stealth UnHoodie</a>, and a California-fleece <a href="/support/cahoodie/">lightweight pullover hoodie</a>. ]]></content>
      <date>1413270000</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[We accept donations via Bitcoin at the following address: 16JPekFQEHyLD4Ji2i2YTWeJjn3iULL2iP  ]]></content>
      <date>1413183600</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[<a href="/dronezone/">Drone Zone is proud to premiere</a> Steve Brand's newest release, The Space Between, on October 3rd, at 8pm Eastern, 5pm Pacific. ]]></content>
      <date>1410937200</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[Indie Pop Rock fans: SomaFM Presents <a href="http://www.theindependentsf.com/event/602701-sondre-lerche-san-francisco/" target="_new">Sondre Lerche at the Independent on October 9th</a> in San Francisco. DJ Elise spinning before and after, hope to see you there. ]]></content>
      <date>1410764400</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[The technical issues with DEF CON radio have been resolved, and it's and it's back on the air. ]]></content>
      <date>1410505200</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[Our Android app has been <a href="/mobile/android.html">updated</a>. Please update to the latest release. iOS app update is waiting for Apple approval but expected to be out soon. ]]></content>
      <date>1409986800</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[Other than giving us a scare, the earthquake that struck the SF Bay area early Sunday morning did no damage to SomaFM's studios or datacenter facilities. ]]></content>
      <date>1408863600</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who came out to say hi at the 20th Street Block Party! So great to meet so many of you. We'll have podcasts from our band interviews posted later in the week. ]]></content>
      <date>1408777200</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[SomaFM will be broadcasting live from the <a href="http://20thstreetblockparty.com" target="_new" >20th Street Block Party</a> this Saturday, from Noon-6pm in San Francisco, inside Sightglass Coffee. Come say hello! ]]></content>
      <date>1408345200</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[Starting now through Sunday, SomaFM's DEF CON Radio will be broadcasting <b>Live</b> from DEF CON 22's chill room in the Rio Hotel in Las Vegas. <a href="/defcon/">Tune in Now</a>! ]]></content>
      <date>1407394800</date>
    </item>
    <item>
      <content><![CDATA[SomaFM and Projekt Records present the album premiere of Steve Roach's "The Delicate Forever" on <a href="/dronezone/">Drone Zone</a>, July 22nd at Noon Pacific Time, 3pm Eastern, 8pm (20:00) GMT. ]]></content>
      <date>1405753200</date>
    </item>
  </items>
</news>