<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<guitars>
    <guitar>
        <make>Gibson</make>
        <model>Les Paul</model>
        <introyear>1952</introyear>
        <desc>The Les Paul was designed by Ted McCarty in collaboration with popular guitarist Les Paul, whom Gibson enlisted to endorse the new model.</desc>
        <image>lespaul.jpg</image>
        <link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gibson_Les_Paul</link>
    </guitar>
    <guitar>
        <make>Gibson</make>
        <model>SG</model>
        <introyear>1961</introyear>
        <desc>The SG generally has a solid mahogany body, with a black bat-wing pickguard. The 24.75" scale mahogany neck joins the body at the 19th fret. The SG's set neck is shallower than the Gibson Les Paul's, but features the traditional Gibson combination of two humbucker pickups and a Tune-o-matic bridge assembly.</desc>
        <image>sg.jpg</image>
        <link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Gibson_sg</link>
    </guitar>
    <guitar>
        <make>Fender</make>
        <model>Stratocaster</model>
        <introyear>1954</introyear>
        <desc>The Fender Stratocaster is an electric guitar designed by Leo Fender, George Fullerton, and Freddie Tavares. It is a double-cutaway guitar, with an extended top horn for balance. Along with the Gibson Les Paul, it is one of the most popularly copied electric guitar shapes.</desc>
        <image>strat.jpg</image>
        <link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fender_Stratocaster</link>
    </guitar>
    <guitar>
        <make>Fender</make>
        <model>Telecaster</model>
        <introyear>1950</introyear>
        <desc>The Fender Telecaster is typically a dual-pickup, solid-body electric guitar. Its simple yet effective design and revolutionary sound broke ground and set trends in electric guitar manufacturing and popular music. Introduced for national distribution as the Broadcaster in the autumn of 1950, it was the first guitar of its kind produced on a substantial scale.</desc>
        <image>tele.jpg</image>
        <link>http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Fender_Telecaster</link>
    </guitar>
</guitars>